{
    "subject": "resource/Arizona_Territory",
    "predicate": "ontology/capital",
    "object": "resource/Tucson,_Arizona",
    "human_readable": "The capital of Arizona Territory is Tucson, Arizona.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9391714334487915,
            "question": "Was Tucson always the capital of Arizona Territory?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9169399738311768,
            "question": "What is the capital of Arizona Territory?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9059783816337585,
            "question": "How has Tucson changed since it served as the capital of Arizona Territory?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7109933495521545,
            "question": "Who were some notable figures associated with Tucson during its time as the capital?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.667975664138794,
            "question": "Are there any remnants or landmarks in Tucson that reflect its time as the capital?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5939404964447021,
            "question": "Where is Tucson located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5022392272949219,
            "question": "Name a significant historical event that occurred in Tucson."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4581887722015381,
            "question": "What factors might have influenced the decision to make Tucson the capital?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4075259268283844,
            "question": "When did Arizona become a territory?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3680792450904846,
            "question": "What state is Arizona?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The capital of Arizona Territory is Tucson, Arizona.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9322_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When did Arizona become a territory?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9322_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What factors might have influenced the decision to make Tucson the capital?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9322_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a significant historical event that occurred in Tucson.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9322_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9322_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9322_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9322_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9322_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9322_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9322_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9322_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9322_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9322_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9322_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe documents clearly state that Tucson served as the capital of the Arizona Territory from 1867 to 1877.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that Tucson served as the capital of the Arizona Territory from 1867 to 1877. This supports the statement that Tucson was the capital of Arizona Territory."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Although Tucson served as the capital of the Arizona Territory from 1867 to 1877, the capital was later moved back to Prescott before finally being moved to Phoenix. So, the capital of Arizona Territory during its existence was not consistently Tucson.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Multiple sources state that Tucson served as the capital of the Arizona Territory from 1867 to 1877, not continuously. Additionally, other locations like Prescott and Phoenix held the position before and after Tucson's tenure.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The capital of the Arizona Territory was moved from Tucson to Prescott in 1877, and then again to Phoenix before Arizona became a state.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context indicates that Tucson served as the capital of the Arizona Territory from 1867 to 1877, not continuously since the territory was formed. Additionally, it mentions that prior to Tucson becoming the capital in 1867, the territorial capital was in Prescott and before Fort Whipple in Chino Valley.",
            "category": -1
        }
    }
}